Jamie Joseph Heiney

Controller

About Me

I am an experienced accountant with expertise in Accounts Payable/Accounts Receivable, Bank & Credit Card Reconciliation, QuickBooks, Google Sheets, Excel Cash Flow Management, Budgeting and Financial Planning. In addition, I have a talent for simplifying complex topics and excellent communication skills.

Skills

- Accounts Payable/Accounts Receivable (AP/AR)
- Bank & Credit Card Reconciliation
- QuickBooks (Enterprise and Online)
- Google Sheets
- Excel Cash Flow Management
- Budgeting and Financial Planning
- Excellent communication
- Simplification of complex topics

Experience

Accountant at Alpha Capital LLC

Dec 2019 - May 2022

- Managed all bookkeeping needs for several capital funding companies including creating chart of accounts, bank reconciliation, organizing, formatting, and importing large amounts of data from CRMS, other software and google sheets.
- Designed and implemented a comprehensive loan tracking system using multiple interlinked Google Sheets and Google App Scripts. The system allowed owners, salespeople, and outside investors to view and update vital information about current and former deals, with multiple permission levels and an intuitive UI.
- Utilized the accounting system for multiple companies owned by Alpha Capital and provided consulting services to other companies.

Nursing Home Game Creator at Games 4 Life

Feb 2017 - Feb 2019

- Developed interactive group games for elderly care facilities to address the lack of stimulating and engaging content for elders.
- Grew client base to over 30 nursing homes and hundreds of happy users.
- Managed accounts receivable and gained a broad understanding of business and management.

AP Regional Manager at Beyond Healthcare LLC

Jan 2015 – Mar 2017

- Oversaw AP transactions and personnel for four nursing homes.
- Negotiated with vendors for more favorable contracts.
- Maintained all accounts payable reports, spreadsheets, and files.
- Acted as a liaison between corporate and nursing home accounts payable departments.
- Managed emails and website domains for the corporate staff.

Education

Certificate in Accounting Foundations

Accounting Foundations: Bookkeeping QuickBooks

Online Essential Training QuickBooks Pro Essential Training Yeshiva Toras Chaim High School Diploma – May 2008, 3.4 GPA Dual Enrolment Florida International University

Accounting Course

Accounting Coach course by Harold Averkamp

Tested and received

Contact: 305-801-7497